let quiz=[
    {
        question:"The Battle of Plassey was fought in",
        option:[
             "1757", 
             "174,8", 
             "1782,", 
             "1764,", 
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Who served as the first Deputy Prime Minister of independent India ? ",
        option:[
             "K.Kamaraj", 
             "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel", 
             "C.Rajagopalachari", 
             "Moraji Desai", 
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Who was the first Governor- General of India?",
        option:[
             "Lord William Bentick", 
             "Warren Hastings", 
             "Lord Canning", 
             "Lord Mountbatten", 
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Who was also known as 'The Light of Asia'?",
        option:[
             "Rumi", 
             "Buddha", 
             "Gandhi", 
             "Swami vivekananda", 
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"India's first mission to the moon was launched in which year?",
        option:[
             "1969", 
             "2,008", 
             "1998", 
             "2,005", 
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:" Which Rajput dynasty did not surrender to Akbar?",
        option:[
             "Parmar dynasty", 
             "Chauhan dynasty", 
             "Chandela dynasty", 
             "Sisodia dynasty", 
        ],
        answer:4,
    },
    {
        question:"Who was adorned with the title of 'Jarikalam' by Emperor Akbar?",
        option:[
             "Muhammed Khan", 
             "Mir Syed Ali", 
             "Abdusamad", 
             "Muhammed Hussain", 
        ],
        answer:4,
    }, 
    {
        question:"What was the real name of Chanakya?",
        option:[
             "Vishnu Gupta", 
             "Ramatanu Mishra", 
             "Kautilya", 
             "None of these", 
        ],
        answer:1,
    }, 
    {
        question:" Which was the first National News Agency of India?",
        option:[
             "The Free Press of India", 
             "The Asoociated Press of India", 
             "The Indian Review", 
             "None of the Above", 
        ],
        answer:1,
    }, 
    {
        question:"When did the Chola Empire of the South emerged?",
        option:[
             "9th Century BC", 
             "19th Century BC", 
             "9th Century AD", 
             "17th Century Ad", 
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
];

